Finding Aid for Sheet music of University of Michigan songs and music, 1894-1947
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Sheet music of University of Michigan songs and music 1894-1947
[Sheet music of University of Michigan songs and music]
0.4 linear feet
FImu F3i
Loose sheet music of University of Michigan songs and music including marches, sports songs and cheers, instrumental works, and various arrangements of "The Yellow and Blue" and "The Victor's."
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Collection acquired from a number of different sources and assembled by Bentley staff.
No additional titles are expected, though new or better copies of existing title may be acquired.
The collection is open to research.
The collection acquired from a number of different sources and assembled by Bentley staff.
The collection consists of loose sheet music of University of Michigan songs and music including marches, sports songs and cheers, instrumental works, and various arrangements of "The Yellow and Blue" and "The Victor's." The collection is arranged by song title.
Subjects:
University of Michigan--Songs and music.
- Sheet music of Michigan songs and music
  - Bluebook Blues. Words by A. L. Weeks. Music by A. J. Gornetzky. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1918 (Box 1)
  - Cheer, Cheer, Cheer for Michigan. Words and music by Lee Tann, 1947 (Box 1)
  - College Days: "Koanzaland." Words by Donald A. Kahn. Music by Earl V. Moore. Unison vocal with piano accompaniment, four part vocal chorus, 1912, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Dear Old Michigan. Words by C. Arthur Blass. Music by Julius Wuerthner. Published by Brehm Bros., Erie Pa., 1910 (Box 1)
  - Fight Men of Michigan: March and Two Step. Words and music by William C. Archi. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1915, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Fighting S.A.T.C. Words by Oscar A. Adel and A. J. Levin. Music by A. J. Gornetzky. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1918 (Box 1)
  - Hail Michigan. Words and music by Claudius G. Pendill. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, chord symbols for guitar, ukulele, banjo, or accordion; chart for guitar, 1941. 4 copies (signed) (Box 1)
  - Hail Michigan. Music by Rowland W. Fixel. Words by Sylvan S. Grosner. Published by University Music House, Ann Arbor, Mich., 1912 (Box 1)
  - I'm a Goin' to Go to Ypsilanti. Words by C. Arthur Blass. Music by Julius Wuerthner. Published by Brehm Bros., Erie, Pa., 1910 (Box 1)
  - Jingles: A College March and Two-Step. Composed by M. B. Cooper. Arranged by Harry Turner. Piano, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Laudes Atque Carmina. Arranged by Florence Shirley (Box 1)
  - Men of Michigan. Words by Bob Elbel. Music by Bob Elbel -- Wm. Revelli. Original Manuscript ed., 1936 (Box 1)
  - Men of Yost: Football March-Two-Step. Composed by M. B. Cooper. Arranged by Harry Turner. Piano, 1904, 5 copies (Box 1)
  - Men of Yost: Michigan's Football Song. Composed by M. B. Cooper. Arranged by E. R. Schremser. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1905 (Box 1)
  - Michigan: March and Two Step. Martha Dickinson Taylor. (With words of The Yellow and Blue by Charles M. Gayley.) Piano, vocal, 1902, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - The Michigan Field Song. Words by Lyman Bryson. Music by Roy Dickinson Welch. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1910., 2 copies (Box 1)
  - Michigan Forever: A March Song. Words by S. N. Lagatree. Music by W. N. Moffett. Vocal with piano accompaniment, 1906 (Box 1)
  - Michigan, Goodbye. [Words by] Donald A. Kahn, J. Fred Lawton. [Music by] Earl V. Moore. [Published by] University of Michigan Union Opera, 1909 (Box 1)
  - Michigan Memories. By John W. Stout. Commissioned by Dr. and Mrs. Fleming A. Barbour. Arrangement for orchestra, circa 1982 (Box 1)
  - Michigan's Men of Steel. Words and music by Roy Dickinson Welch. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1913 (Box 1)
  - Next to the Grand Old Flag Comes the Yellow and Blue. By Walker M. Lang. Published by Jerome H. Remick & Co., Detroit and New York, 1910 (Box 1)
  - O Alma Mater: Michigan University Song. By Roy Dickinson Welch. Four part vocal with piano accompaniment, 1908 (Box 1)
  - Stadium March: A Michigan Marching Song. Words by Allis F. Hussey. Music by Carl E. Gehring. Vocal with piano accompaniment, trumpet fanfare, 1926 (Box 1)
  - That Michigan Band. By C. D. Kountz and Harry Turner. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment 1914, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - 'Tis of Michigan We Sing. Author of first stanza unknown. Second and third stanzas and chorus by Edmund S. C. May. Music adapted from "Lizette." (Box 1)
  - U of M Waltz. By Lew H. Clement. Piano arrangement for dancing, 1894 (Box 1)
  - Varsity.
    - Music by Earl V. Moore. Arranged for orchestra by S. Deshon 1911 (Box 1)
    - Music by Earl V. Moore. Arranged for [Michigan Marching band] by Tom Clark (Box 1)
    - Words by Fred J. Lawton. Music by Earl V. Moore. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment 1911, 4 copies
  - Varsity Days: Introducing the Michigan Drinking Song. By C. M. Foss. Arranged for piano, 1903 (Box 1)
  - Varsity March. Arranged by Roscoe M. Gage. Arrangements for guitar, first mandolin, second mandolin, undated (Box 1)
  - The Victors: March. By Louis Elbel.
    - Arranged for piano 1899, 6 copies (Box 1)
    - Arranged for mandolin, guitar 1899
  - Win for Michigan: A Field Song. By William T. Whedon. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1913, 2 copies (Box 1)
  - The Yellow and Blue. Words by Charles M. Gayley. Music by Balfe.
    - Arranged by Earl Killeen. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment; four part vocal 1908 (Box 1)
    - Vocal solo with piano accompaniment 1928 (Box 1)
  - The Yellow and Blue: Two Step. By Leon M. Jones. Vocal solo with piano accompaniment, 1895 (Box 1)